<?xml version="1.0"?>
<newsItems num="10">

<news main="false"><date>09/16/10</date><title>The Original Lifestyle</title><content><paragraph>What's new? We are. OGK Clothing, Original Kuruption: The Original Lifestyle.  Revolutionary trends and designs inspired from nothing but originality.&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Our first shipment will be an order of t-shirts that are in the design process now. You can view the concepts of these designs by clicking "Guys" or "Girls" from the above menu.  Keep coming back to check for updates like when our shipment arrives and when these products are available for purchase.  Join us on Facebook and follow us on Twitter by clicking on "Contact".</paragraph></content><id>2</id><user>JordanHeemskerk</user><imageURL>nodirectory</imageURL></news><news main="false"><date>11/06/10</date><title>Finalized First Order</title><content><paragraph>Great news! Our first order has been finalized and will be released for sale shortly. Make sure if you want something, especially in a specific size, to contact us and ask us to hold it for you. We are expecting to sell out of certain sizes of product FAST!!! Of course, as soon as we sell out, we will be introducing new designs! &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Among the finalized products are the OGK Neon Hoodie, and the OGK Cross Crewneck! These late-release products were added on to the order last minute for the winter season and are in low supply. &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Check back soon to see when these first-releases are available for purchase (trust us, really soon).&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>We appreciate all the support, The OgK Crew</paragraph></content><id>3</id><user>JordanHeemskerk</user><imageURL>nodirectory</imageURL></news><news main="false"><date>11/12/10</date><title>First Order Has Arrived!</title><content><paragraph>Phenomenal news, our first shipment had arrived! We have the OgK Classic Guys Tee, The OgK Fade Girls Tee, and the OgK Neon Guys Hoodie (which still looks good on the ladies!). These items are for sale effective immediately! The OgK Cross Crew Neck will be arriving shortly, due to some shipping delays, but it will hopefully be available for purchase within the next week. &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Like we projected, some sizes are selling out fast. Get yours while they last, as this order is unique in the fact that these shirts may never be produced again. &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>So get in touch with Trevor, Jordan or Naz, or order IMMEDIATELY online, and get your OgK on your back as soon as possible.&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>On another note, today is November 12th, that's only 43 days to go until Christmas, and only 42 days to finish up your dreaded Christmas shopping. Make your Christmas shopping easy, OgK is a great gift for any age! &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Till Next Time, (Yeah, probably around next week)&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>The OgK Crew</paragraph></content><id>5</id><user>JordanHeemskerk</user><imageURL>nodirectory</imageURL></news><news main="false"><date>11/17/10</date><title>Crew Necks!</title><content><paragraph>Just a quick update for the OgK family! We recently recieved our shipment of crew necks! You may either order online, or if you are in the Greater Victoria area contact Naz, Trevor or Jordan (contact info on contact page).&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Thanks everyone&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>-Ogk Crew</paragraph></content><id>6</id><user>NazKhedri</user><imageURL>nodirectory</imageURL></news><news main="false"><date>11/21/10</date><title>What's Been Happening at OgK</title><content><paragraph>Check out the new Media page by clicking the Media link at the top of the page. Our new video CREATE.Originality is there along with a "What We're Listening To" section that will be updated bi-weekly. &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>On a change of subject, all our products featured on this site are now available for sale. Order online with your credit card today! Keep an eye out for OgK around you; you can't miss those OgK Classic Shirts!&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>OgK is looking for Models. Send us an email if you are interested in doing a photo-shoot with us! Our next design phase is also beginning. If you have an ORIGINAL IDEA that you want to see OgK feature in their new line, send us an email (check the Contact Page). &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Remember to like us on Facebook and follow us on Twitter.&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph> </paragraph></content><id>7</id><user>JordanHeemskerk</user><imageURL>nodirectory</imageURL></news><news main="false"><date>11/29/10</date><title>Boarding Season Around The Corner!</title><content><paragraph>Long time no see! &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>With the peak of the snowboarding and skiing season just around the corner, OgK is teeming with excitement! Who thinks some OgK Toques are in order? We're busy waxing and prepping our gear and we're wondering how ready are you for the season! And remember to pray to the snow gods for powder-ridden slopes during this La Nina Winter! That's right, this is supposed to be our coldest winter for a while. You might consider the OgK Neon Hoodie, or the OgK Cross Crew Neck (check the Guy's Page), to keep you from freezing to death out there! &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Remember to send us your original design ideas! If we pick your design to make, you will receive a free article of whatever you designed!&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>We still need some models for our photo-shoots. Drop as a line (check the Contact Page) and let us know if you want to be a part of the OgK Revolution.&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>See you on the slopes!&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph/></content><id>8</id><user>JordanHeemskerk</user><imageURL>nodirectory</imageURL></news><news main="false"><date>12/14/10</date><title>Better Be Quick</title><content><paragraph>Just a heads up to everyone out there. We have sold over half of our first order. In fact, we are completely sold out of some sizing in certain products. So, this means that if you are wanting to buy, you need to get in touch with Jordan, Trevor or Naz immediately so that you can get your OgK before the first order is completely gone. &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>On more of a forward note, what do you think should be included in the second release? Tee's? Hoodies? Let us know if there is something you want OgK to explore!&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Finally, it's that time of the year again, with Christmas less than 2 weeks away, OgK makes a great quick and easy gift for that hard to buy for person!&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Till next time, that's all from OgK.&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph/></content><id>9</id><user>JordanHeemskerk</user><imageURL>nodirectory</imageURL></news><news main="true"><date>01/02/11</date><title>Best Wishes</title><content><paragraph>From all of us at OgK Clothing, we wish you all the happiness in 2011. &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Expect to see a lot more of OgK in the New Year, and watch out for new releases when they become available. Items from our first order have almost been depleted, so if you are wanting something from the limited edition first order, get in touch with us by visiting the contact page, or order online.&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Also, OgK is working on a top secret project; keep posted for when its announced.&#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>Happy New Year, &#xD;</paragraph><paragraph>OgK</paragraph></content><id>10</id><user>JordanHeemskerk</user><imageURL>nodirectory</imageURL></news></newsItems>
